I'm gonna tell y'all exactly what I'm doing right now. I'm sitting on my floor in my closet
between about to go take a shower and I look at my phone and I see this interview with Bernie
Sanders where this man will not say that there's a genocide happening in Chesa. And I got so angry
because I think part of the reason and I don't know if y'all feel the same way part of the reason
I feel so angry these days and so just like discordant is because I feel like I just I got
got. First of all I was in a three-year relationship with a nigga who ended up being a complete fraud so
I feel like I got got there. Then like I'm going through it with realizing that you know
parents are people so you feel like you got got there but then the world is just not at all what
I feel like me as a smart conscious person even thought it was. And I feel like I'm in a constant
state of goddage. Is it just me? And then I look at these people and I just did a political comedy
documentary in July of last year where I had respect and regard for the role that politicians play and for
what they do. And within the last nine months I have conceived, gestated, and birthed a whole new
radicalism and consciousness around the absolute perfunctory purpose of these individuals.
And I see them and I see that we the interviews that happen with them we end up having to have a
certain level of respect and regard especially because you know in the case of them being elders
but ultimately they're charlatans. They're charlatans and it's incensing. It's incensing to witness.
It's incensing to watch. It's demoralizing. It's disenchanting. It's so many things.
And it is one of the things that daily renders me to tears. One of the things. And sometimes I just
wish that I had the opportunity to interview these people and really be like what the fuck yo? What
the fuck? And I know I would probably only get one interview because they wouldn't come back.
But I just I don't know. And that drives me crazy. I don't know.